Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1 5583/1
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Box: 4, Folder: 7 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Item 6: Handling Grievances, Publication (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Item 7: Alcoans in the American Tradition, Publication (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Item 8: Alcoa is Opportunity, Publication (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Item 9: Would you like Alcoa?, Publication (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Item 10: Alcoa Careers in Administration, Publication (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Item 11: Alcoa 79, Publication (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Item 12: Alcoa Policy Guidelines for Business Conduct, Publication (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Box: 4, Folder: 8 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Bulletin; Peoples Section; Vol 4. No. 2, Publication (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Bulletin; Peoples Section; Vol 4. No. 5, Publication (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Box: 4, Folder: 9 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: This is the ABA, Publication (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: A Guide to the American Bankers Assoc. Library, Publication (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: How to Train a Bank Proof and Transit Clerk, Publication (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: The Drafting of a Banker's Code, Publication (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Item 5: Aids from ABA, Publication (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Item 6: Handbook for Training the Disadvantaged, Publication (Box 4, Folder 9)
    By Robert Albright, Lloyd Jones. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Government Relations Status Report, Publication (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Item 8: Aids from ABA, Publication (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Box: 4, Folder: 10 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Group Life Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: Employees' Retirement System, Publication (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: Comprehensive Group Insurance Plan for California Employees, Publication (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Item 4: The Three Fundamentals that Make a Company, Publication (Box 4, Folder 10)
    By Wm. B. Given, Jr. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Brake Shoe Yardsticks, Publication (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Item 6: Messages to the Brake Shoe Organization, Publication (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Item 7: Freedom to Manage, Publication (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Item 8: Leadership in Operations, Publication (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Item 9: Brake Shoe News: Special Issue, Publication (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Item 10: Our Nurses and Their Opportunity, Publication (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Box: 4, Folder: 11 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Employing the Older Worker in the Food Service Industry, Publication (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Box: 4, Folder: 12 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: The First Twenty-Five Years: 1953-1977, Publication (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Box: 4, Folder: 13 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Immediate Problems, Publication (Box 4, Folder 13)
    By Otto H. Kahn. Item is in English.
- Box: 4, Folder: 14 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Signs of the Times, Publication (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Item 2: Job Rating, Publication (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Item 3: Employer-Employee Communications, Publication (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Item 4: Briefing Session No. 5, Publication (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Item 5: Three Concurrent Roundtables, Publication (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Item 6: Roundtable Discussion Flyers, Publication (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Item 7: Vital Issues in Industrial Relations, Publication (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Item 8: Job Rating, Publication (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Item 9: Job Rating, Publication (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Item 10: Job Rating Manual, Publication (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Box: 4, Folder: 15 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: A Guide to Labor Arbitration Clauses, Publication (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Item 2: Do you write Invisible Clauses, Publication (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Item 3: Arbitration News, Publication (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Item 4: A Businessman's Guide to Commercial Arbitration, Publication (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Item 5: President's Report, Publication (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Item 6: Arbitration as a Business Tool, Publication (Box 4, Folder 15)
    By R. Emerson Swart. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Arbitration News, Publication (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Item 8: The AAA In its 40th Year, Publication (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Item 9: Labor Arbitration, Publication (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Item 10: Standards of Practice for Arbitration, Publication (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Item 11: Voluntary Labor Arbitration Rules, Publication (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Item 12: 33 Questions, Publication (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Item 13: Suggestions for Members of Panels when Acting as Arbitrators under its Rules, Publication (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Item 14: Code of Ethics for Arbitrators, Publication (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Item 15: How to Select an Arbitrator, Publication (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Item 16: A Brief Description of AAA, Publication (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Item 17: How to Protect Your Foreign Trade, Publication (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Item 18: Facts about the AAA, Publication (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Item 19: Sample of Official Secret Ballot, Publication (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Item 20: Questions and Answers, Publication (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Box: 4, Folder: 16 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Voluntary Labor Arbitration Rules, Publication (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Item 2: Why Unions and Companies use AAA, Publication (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Item 3: 50th Anniversary Program, Publication (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Item 4: Labor Management Pamphlet, Publication (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Item 5: Arbitration News, Publication (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Item 6: Construction Industry Arbitration Rules, Publication (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Item 7: Voluntary Labor Arbitration Rules, Publication (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Item 8: The Press Speaks for Arbitration, Publication (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Item 9: 9 Ways to Cut Arbitration Costs, Publication (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Item 10: Due Process in Labor Arbitration, Publication (Box 4, Folder 16)
    By Morris Stone. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: You be the Arbitrator!, Publication (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Item 12: Code of Ethics for Arbitrators, Publication (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Item 13: Toward Effective Arbitration, Publication (Box 4, Folder 16)
    By J. Noble Braden. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Voluntary Labor Arbitration Rules, Publication (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Item 15: Blue Book, Publication (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Item 16: Voluntary Labor Arbitration Rules, Publication (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Item 17: Voluntary Labor Arbitration Rules, Publication (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Item 18: Code of Ethics for Arbitrators, Publication (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Item 19: The American Arbitrator and His Office, Publication (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Item 20: Labor Arbitration, Publication (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Box: 4, Folder: 17 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Problems of the National Labor Relations Board, Publication (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Item 2: Can Unemployment be Ended, Publication (Box 4, Folder 17)
    By Rt. Rev. Msgr. John A Ryan, D.D. Item is in English.
- Box: 4, Folder: 18 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Letter to Members re. 29th Annual Conference, Publication (Box 4, Folder 18)
    By John J. McGovern. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Awards, Publication (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Item 3: Communication, Publication (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Item 4: Communication, Publication (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Item 5: How Advertising Can Use Psychology's Rules of Learning, Publication (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Item 6: Rising Level of Education of the Public, Publication (Box 4, Folder 18)
    By S.I. Hayakawa. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Conference Report, Publication (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Item 8: Summaries of Speeches and Events at 25th Annual Conference, Publication (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Item 9: Letter to Members, Publication (Box 4, Folder 18)
    By Dennison R. Crandall. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Constitution and By-Laws, Publication (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Item 11: Constitution and By-Laws, Publication (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Item 12: Constitution and By-Laws, Publication (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Item 13: Annual Convention Advertisement, Publication (Box 4, Folder 18)
    By Ellwood Witt. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: The Eternal Spring, Publication (Box 4, Folder 18)
    By Wilfred Talman. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Summary of Presentations at Annual 1957 Convention, Publication (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Box: 4, Folder: 19 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Training Manual, Publication (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Box: 4, Folder: 20 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Employment Opportunities in the Aluminum Industry, Publication (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Item 2: Expanding Markets for Aluminum, Publication (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Item 3: Aluminum Association Directory, Publication (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Item 4: Employment Outlook for Aluminum Manufacturing, Publication (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Box: 4, Folder: 21 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Getting Acquainted, Publication (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Box: 4, Folder: 22 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Rules of Conduct & Rules and Regulation for the Construction Camp, Publication (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Box: 4, Folder: 23 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Fact and Background re. Pilot Strike, Publication (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Item 2: Monthly Safety Letter, Publication (Box 4, Folder 23)
    By R.W. Knight. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Monthly Safety Letter, Publication (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Item 4: Ground and Flight Safety Programs, Publication (Box 4, Folder 23)
    By I.C. McInnis. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Safe Operations, Publication (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Item 6: Pension Plan, Publication (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Item 7: Group Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Item 8: Group Dental Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Item 9: Attendance Control, Publication (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Box: 4, Folder: 24 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: An Analysis of the Unanimous Decision of the Supreme Court of MA Declaring the Anti-Injunction Law of that State Unconstitutional, Publication (Box 4, Folder 24)
    By Daniel Davenport. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Letter to Members re. Arkansas Coal Cases Verdict Against United Mine Workers, Publication (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Item 3: Labor Unions and the Law, Publication (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Box: 5, Folder: 1 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations Manual; Vol. 1: 1.99-1.661.106, Publication (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Box: 5, Folder: 2 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations Manual; Vol. 1: 1.100.050-1.551.142, Publication (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Box: 5, Folder: 3 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations Manual; Vol. 1: 1.00.00.01-1.17.11.04, Publication (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Box: 5, Folder: 4 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations Manual; Vol. 4: 4.29.14.01-4.37.21.04, Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Box: 5, Folder: 5 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations Manual; Vol. 4: 4.39.62.01-4.56.63.1, Publication (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Box: 5, Folder: 6 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations Manual; Vol. 4: 4.60.00.01-4.76.63.31, Publication (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Box: 5, Folder: 7 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations Manual; Vol. 4: 4.76.63.32-4.200.007, Publication (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Box: 5, Folder: 8 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations Manual; Vol. 4: 4.71.34.01-4.81.34.27, Publication (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Box: 5, Folder: 9 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations Manual; Vol. 4: 4.64.65.01-4.70.63.10, Publication (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Box: 5, Folder: 10 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations Manual; Vol. 4: 4.82.34.01-4.84.63.08, Publication (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Box: 5, Folder: 11 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations Manual; Vol. 4: 4.86.11.01-4.90.62.24, Publication (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Box: 5, Folder: 12 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations Manual; Vol. 4: 4.91.63.01-4.200.03.12, Publication (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Box: 6, Folder: 1 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations Instructions Superseded Sheets: 4.43.34.00-4.51.63.22, Publication (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Box: 6, Folder: 2 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations Manual; Vol 4: 4.M.1-4.9x.63.24, Publication (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Box: 6, Folder: 3 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations Manual; Vol 4: 4.10.27.01-4.25.09.21, Publication (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Box: 6, Folder: 4 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations Manual; Vol 11: 1.112, 11.100.001-11.901.011, Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Box: 6, Folder: 5 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations Manual; Vol 11: 1.112, 11.2-11.770.003, Publication (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Box: 6, Folder: 6 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations Instructions Superseded Sheets: 1.00.01.01-1.261.501, Publication (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Box: 6, Folder: 7 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations Instructions Superseded Sheets: 4.59.64.B.01-4.63.100.21, Publication (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Box: 6, Folder: 8 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations Instructions Superseded Sheets: 4.64.65.01-4.68.63B.29, Publication (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Box: 7, Folder: 1 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations Instructions Superseded Sheets: 4.70.34.01-4.71.97.26, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Box: 7, Folder: 2 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations Instructions Superseded Sheets: 4.37.09.01-4.42.63.34, Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Box: 7, Folder: 3 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations Instructions Superseded Sheets: 4.00.7-4.49.2 (Amendments), Publication (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Box: 7, Folder: 4 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations Instructions Superseded Sheets: 4.81.34.01-4.84.63.32, Publication (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Box: 7, Folder: 5 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations Superseded Sheets: 4.86.11.01-4.89.63.26, Publication (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Box: 7, Folder: 6 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations Superseded Sheets: 4.10.27.01-4.19.34.11, Publication (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Box: 7, Folder: 7 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Amendments 1.00-3.50, Publication (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Box: 8, Folder: 1 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Sperry Gyroscope Job Evaluation Material, Publication (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Box: 8, Folder: 2 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Superseded Sheets; 2.100.101-2.760.259, Publication (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Box: 8, Folder: 3 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Amendments 4.50-11.2, Publication (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Box: 8, Folder: 4 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Superseded Sheets; 4.59.64B.01-4.63.100.21, Publication (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Box: 8, Folder: 5 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Superseded Sheets; 4.20.41.01-4.25.90.07, Publication (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Box: 8, Folder: 6 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Superseded Sheets; 3.00.01.01-4.9x.63.19, Publication (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Box: 9, Folder: 1 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Superseded Sheets; 4.94.21.01-4.99.63.10, Publication (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Box: 9, Folder: 2 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Superseded Sheets; 4.9x.63.01-4.9x.63.17, Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Box: 9, Folder: 3 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Superseded Sheets; 4.90.21.01-4.93.21.11, Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Box: 9, Folder: 4 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Superseded Sheets; 1.391.101-1.928.002, Publication (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Box: 9, Folder: 5 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Superseded Sheets; 4.26.85.08-4.33.21.29, Publication (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Box: 9, Folder: 6 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Superseded Sheets; 4.34.02.01-4.36.34.31, Publication (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Box: 9, Folder: 7 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Superseded Sheets; 4.34.02.01-4.36.34.31, Publication (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Box: 9, Folder: 8 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Superseded Sheets; 4.34.02.01-4.36.34.34, Publication (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Box: 9, Folder: 9 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Superseded Sheets; 4.1.00.63.02-11.901.008, Publication (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Box: 9, Folder: 10 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Superseded Sheets; 4.73.34.01-4.79.21.16, Publication (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Box: 10, Folder: 1 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: What Freedom in New York Schools?, Publication (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: What Rights for the Unemployed, Publication (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Democracy in Trade Unions, Publication (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Box: 10, Folder: 2 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The American Commonwealth Plan, Publication (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Commonwealth Federation of New York Flyer, Publication (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Letter to Miss Coit, Publication (Box 10, Folder 2)
    By Alfred Bingham. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Preamble and Platform, Publication (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Third Party Group Forms, Publication (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Formation of a New Party, Publication (Box 10, Folder 2)
    By Henry Pratt. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Letter to Membership, Publication (Box 10, Folder 2)
    By Nathan Fine. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Letter re. Forum Meeting, Publication (Box 10, Folder 2)
    By Marie MacDonald. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Bulletin, Publication (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Box: 10, Folder: 3 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The Forum; Vol. LXX No. 2, Publication (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Its Purpose, Organization and Activity, Publication (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Semi-Annual Statement, Publication (Box 10, Folder 3)
    By Franklin D. Roosevelt. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Task Ahead for Building, Publication (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Folder re. The Construction Industry, Publication (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Box: 10, Folder: 4 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Tentative Draft of Memorandum, Publication (Box 10, Folder 4)
    By Howard Eaton. Item is in English.
- Box: 10, Folder: 5 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Survey Request to Gulf Oil Co., Publication (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Survey Request to Monsanto Chemical Co., Publication (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Employee Retirement Plan, Publication (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Response to Human Health Needs, Publication (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Industrial Chemicals Division, Publication (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Security Analysts Meeting, Publication (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: Response to Human Health Needs, Publication (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: The New Mythology, Publication (Box 10, Folder 5)
    By Ken Sayers. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Welcome to Cyanamid, Publication (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Item 10: Stamford Research Laboratories, Publication (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Item 11: Lederle: The First Forty Years, Publication (Box 10, Folder 5)
    By B.W. Carey. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: How to Retard Recovery, Publication (Box 10, Folder 5)
    By W.B. Bell. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Evaluation Questionnaire: Action Course in Practical Politics, Publication (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Item 14: Evaluation Questionnaire: Freedom vs. Communism, Publication (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Item 15: Report: Cyanamid in Civic Affairs, Publication (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Item 16: Voting Calendar, Publication (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Item 17: ACCO News, Publication (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Item 18: Bound Brook Diamond, Publication (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Item 19: Cyanamid News, Publication (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Item 20: The Formican, Publication (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Item 21: Employees Retirement Plan, Publication (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Item 22: Employees Retirement Plan, Publication (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Item 23: Your Life with Calco, Publication (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Item 24: Employees Group Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Item 25: Survey Request to American Cyanamid, Publication (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Item 26: Survey Request to Rockwell Manufacturing, Publication (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Item 27: Survey Request to Koppers Co., Inc., Publication (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Item 28: Survey Request to Ford Motor Co., Publication (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Item 29: Survey Request to Household Finance Corporation, Publication (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Box: 10, Folder: 6 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Lower Costs Through Human Engineering, Publication (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: The Great Delusion, Publication (Box 10, Folder 6)
    By Andrew Kaul, III. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Who Gets How Much for Doing What in American, Publication (Box 10, Folder 6)
    By E. Keller, F. Clark and R.S. Rimanoczy. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Memo, Publication (Box 10, Folder 6)
    By J.E. Canning. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Would Wage Incentives Promote Industrial Peace?, Publication (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Box: 10, Folder: 7 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Industry-Wide Collective Bargaining and the Public Interest, Publication (Box 10, Folder 7)
    By John V. Van Sickle. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Automation, Publication (Box 10, Folder 7)
    By Almarin Phillips. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Three Taft-Hartley Issues, Publication (Box 10, Folder 7)
    By Theodore R. Iserman. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Legal Immunities of Labor Unions, Publication (Box 10, Folder 7)
    By Roscoe Pound. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Full Employment Bill, Publication (Box 10, Folder 7)
    By Henry Hazlitt. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Manpower Needs and The Labor Supply, Publication (Box 10, Folder 7)
    By Clarence D. Long. Item is in English.
- Box: 10, Folder: 8 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Special Analysis: National Labor Policy, Publication (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Box: 10, Folder: 9 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Public Policy Forums, Publication (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: Memorandum, Publication (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: Memorandum, Publication (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Box: 10, Folder: 10 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: You and America's Farm Program, Publication (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Box: 10, Folder: 11 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Illinois Small Business Men's Association, Publication (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: Stop Unemployment Compensation Rip-Off, Publication (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Item 3: The Ten Commandments, Publication (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Item 4: A Voluntary Association of Businessmen, Publication (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Box: 10, Folder: 12 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Unions' Wartime Responsibilities, Publication (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Box: 10, Folder: 13 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: A Study of Work Efficiency of Blind and Sighted Workers in Industry, Publication (Box 10, Folder 13)
    By Doglas Cortland MacFarland. Item is in English.
- Box: 10, Folder: 14 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Which Way to Peace?, Publication (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Item 2: Civil Liberties Issue, Publication (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Item 3: Personnel Needs, Publication (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Item 4: Four Projects for Service, Publication (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Item 5: A Reaffirmation of Faith, Publication (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Item 6: If this be Liberty, Publication (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Item 7: Labor Participation in International Affairs, Publication (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Box: 10, Folder: 15 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Address to Membership, Publication (Box 10, Folder 15)
    By Milton A. Herzig. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: By-Laws, Publication (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Item 3: Rules and Procedure for the Arbitration of Disputes in the Fur Trade, Publication (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Box: 10, Folder: 16 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Apprentice Training Standards, Publication (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Box: 10, Folder: 17 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Proposed Reserves of Crude Oil, Natural Gas Liquids and Natural Gas, Publication (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Item 2: Natural Gas Serves Our Community, Publication (Box 10, Folder 17)
    By Burnett Cross. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Essential Elements in Supervisory Development, Publication (Box 10, Folder 17)
    By Robert K. Burns. Item is in English.
- Box: 10, Folder: 18 (Box 10, Folder 18)